Alex Fallaw

Graphic Designer

I'm a graphic design and computer science student at the University of Illinois Urbana-Champaign. I've been passionate about art for almost a decade, experimenting with several different art forms over the years. I have also come to love coding, both web design and program development. I really enjoy the problem-solving involved in programming, and I appreciate the flexibility it gives me in manifesting my designs. I'm looking for an internship or entry-level job in web or graphic design.

Skill Highlights

Digital design WordPress

Instructional graphic design **HTML CSS** Website design

Wireframing Java Collaborative story writing **JavaScript**

Adobe Creative Suite (Photoshop, React JS

Illustrator, InDesign) Git

Figma

SketchBook

Education

University of Illinois Urbana-Champaign Graphic Design, BFA with minor in Computer Science 2022-present

University of Wisconsin Eau Claire **Graphic Communications** 2021-2022

Parkland College **General Studies** 2020-2021

Work Experience

Lowes Cashier

Responsibilities:

Deliver excellent customer service at the register

Answer customer questions

Was awarded a service award for customer service

May 2021 - August 2021

Champaign, IL

House Cleaner

Responsibilities:

Dishes

Vacuuming

General cleaning

December 2019 - August 2021

Champaign, IL